

My resume is online: www.devil.ren Scan the QRcode on the right or search "devilyouwei" on Google

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages

HTML / CSS / JavaScript / PHP / TypeScript / Java / C# / C / Markdown

I am a fast learner and have worked on various different programming languages in the past 6 years.

OS and Tools

Linux / Windows / Vim / Git / Bash / Nginx / npm / Apache / gcc / CI CD

Linux + Vim is my favourite development environment. I have 8 years Linux using experience!

Database

MySQL/MongoDB/SQLServer

I have used different kinds of databases in my projects, mostly use MySQL.

Framework and Model

Vue / React / Jquery / Bootstrap / ThinkPHP / Node Express / Tensorflow.js / Cocos Game Engine

Back-end: Much experience in utilizing the MVC framework development.

Front-end: Much experience in modern front-end like vue and react.

Game: 2D game development experience with Cocos Creator Engine.

Others - Important

Mandarin Chinese (first language) / English (fluent) / Shanghai dialect (mother language)

Taekwondo / Bussiness / Cooking / Finance marketing

I have some experience in managing a company or a team.

WORK EXPERIENCES

2015-2018

Suzhou Pointer Network Technology Company

Suzhou, China

Web Developer, Manager

I established a company in Suzhou City. As a manager, I created and managed the project called 'SunJob'.

2013-2018

West Point TKD

Suzhou, China

Taekwondo Instructor, Taekwondo Referee

Teach Taekwondo (Part-time Job).

2018-2019

Shanghai LeMiao Network Technology Company

Shanghai, China

Front-end, Game Developer, Project Manager

I started and managed a project called **I want to win lipsticks game**, This game owns more than 2 millions active users, it is also the most popular lipsticks game in China. It is developed based on vue for front-end, react-native for native and php for backend

2019-Now

Qbyte LLC

♀ Long Branch, NJ, US

Web Developer

Qbyte LLC is a started company. I found it at MU. Our product is named **Qbite**. Qbite is an online ordering system. Qbite is developed on vue for frontend, bootstrap for our landing page and node for backend.

Want to know more about my experience? Please refer to my GitHub and Blog

EDUCATION

2013-2018

ChangShu Institute of Technology

Suzhou, China

Bachelor's Degree - Software Engineerning

Manager of Student Innovation Lab

I left school to establish a company for one year in 2015 and returned back in 2016.

2019-2020

Monmouth University

♀NJ, US

Master's Degree - Software Engineerning

President of Chinese Student Association

AWARD & ACHIEVEMENTS

Oct 2017

Software Copyright

My mobile app 'Dashen' obtains the national software copyright of the People's Republic Of China.

View Product

View Copyright

March 2018

Publication Of Papers

《Financial data prediction system based on RNN》

This project was completed for my thesis which is about using RNN to predict financial data. It was also then published on a Chinese Software Guide Book.

View Paper In PDF

View Online

20, January 2015

Taekwondo Black Belt 2 Dan

After 10 years of learning taekwondo, I achieved a 2nd Degree black belt from 'World Taekwondo Federation'.

- **▲** Download All My Awards
- **B**log (100,000+ viewers)
- Github (Good open-source repos)
- in LinkedIn
- ✓ Youwei Huang's Website
- ■ devilyouwei@gmail.com
- ■ devilyouwei@foxmail.com
- **4** +1 (732) 268-0284

Copyright © 2020 www.devil.ren name All rights reserved.